{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-1",
			"front": "Gaining entry to an enclosed area and reaching a patient.",
			"back": "access"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-2",
			"front": "The designated field command center where the incident commander and support staff are located.",
			"back": "command post"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-3",
			"front": "Entry that requires special tools and training and includes the use of force.",
			"back": "complex access"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-4",
			"front": "An area where people can be exposed to hazards such as electric wires, sharp metal edges, broken glass, toxic substances, radiation, or fire.",
			"back": "danger zone"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-5",
			"front": "To be caught (trapped) within a vehicle, room, or container with no way out or to have a limb or other body part trapped.",
			"back": "entrapment"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-6",
			"front": "Removal of a patient from entrapment or a dangerous situation or position, such as removal from a wrecked vehicle, industrial incident, or collapsed building.",
			"back": "extrication"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-7",
			"front": "Any substance that is toxic, poisonous, radioactive, flammable, or explosive and causes injury or death with exposure.",
			"back": "hazardous material"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-8",
			"front": "The individual who has overall command of the incident in the field.",
			"back": "incident commander"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-9",
			"front": "An area of protection providing safety from the danger zone (hot zone).",
			"back": "safe zone"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-10",
			"front": "Respirator with independent air supply used by firefighters to enter toxic and otherwise dangerous atmospheres.",
			"back": "self-contained breathing apparatus"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-11",
			"front": "Access that is easily achieved without the use of tools or force.",
			"back": "simple access"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-12",
			"front": "The ongoing process of information gathering and scene evaluation to determine appropriate strategies and tactics to manage an emergency.",
			"back": "size-up"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-13",
			"front": "A specialized law enforcement tactical unit.",
			"back": "special weapons and tactics team"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-14",
			"front": "A fire in a house, apartment building, office, school, plant, warehouse, or other building.",
			"back": "structure fire"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-15",
			"front": "A hostage, robbery, or other situation in which armed conflict is threatened or shots have been fired and the threat of violence remains.",
			"back": "tactical situation"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-16",
			"front": "A team of emergency responders from one or more departments in a region who are trained and on call for certain types of technical rescue.",
			"back": "technical rescue group"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-39-tag-vocabulary-card-17",
			"front": "A rescue that requires special technical skills and equipment in one of many specialized rescue areas, such as technical rope rescue, cave rescue, and dive rescue.",
			"back": "technical rescue situation"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-39",
		"label": "Chapter 39"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "vocabulary",
			"label": "Vocabulary"
		}
	]
}